[
{
    "question": "What is a procedure?",
    "choice1": "A set of iterated statements", 
		"choice2": "A small section of code within a program which performs a task", 
    "choice3": "A decision point in a program",
    "choice4": "None of the following",
    "answer": 2

  },
	{
    "question": "Why are procedures used?",
		"choice1": "None of the following",
		"choice2": "To make code more readable",
		"choice3": "To reduce repetition of code", 
   "choice4": "To make decisions",
   "answer": 3

	},
	{
    "question": "Why are functions used?",
    "choice1": "To make code more readable", 
		"choice2": "To reduce repetition of code and to calculate a value", 
		"choice3": "None of the following",
    "choice4": "To make decisions",
    "answer": 2

  },
	{
    "question": "What is the difference between a function and a procedure?",
    "choice1": "None of the following", 
    "choice2": "A procedure produces a calculated result whereas a function performs a task",
    "choice3": "A procedure iterates code whereas a function is a decision point", 
    "choice4": "A procedure performs a task whereas a funciton produces a calculated result",
    "answer": 2

  }, 
	{
    "question": "What statement is used to create a procedure or function?",
    "choice1": "Make",
		"choice2": "Elif", 
    "choice3": "def", 
    "choice4": "None of the following", 
    "answer": 2 
  },
	{
    "question": "What term is given to running a procedure or function?",
    "choice1": "None of the following",
     "choice2": "call",
     "choice3": "execute", 
    "choice4": "perform", 
    "answer": 3 

	},
	{
    "question": "What term is given to passing back of the value calculated in a function?",
  	"choice1": "overwritten",
    "choice2": "returned",  
    "choice3": "repeated",
    "choice4": "None of the following",
    "answer": 2

	},
	{
    "question": "Which of the following is a procedure?",
    "choice1": "A section of code which converts Farenheit to Celsius",
    "choice2": "A section of code which calculates the VAT on a selling price",
    "choice3": "A section of code which resets all variables to zero", 
    "choice4": "None of the following", 
    "answer": 3

	},
	{
    "question": "Which of the following is a function?",
    "choice1": "A section of code which converts Farenheit to Celsius",
    "choice2": "A section of code which updates a display", 
    "choice3": "A section of code which resets all variables to zero",
    "choice4": "None of the following",
    "answer": 1 
 
	},
	{
    "question": "Why is code indented in a procedure or a function",
    "choice1": "None of the following", 
		"choice2": "To show that it belongs within a procedure or function", 
    "choice3": "To make it more readable", 
    "choice4": "To show that should be iterated", 
    "answer": 2 
 
	}
]